radarbox24.com 2019-03-30

# RadarBox Privacy Policy - AirNav RadarBox - Live Flight Tracker and Airport Status

Welcome to **AirNav Systems LLC** (“AirNav”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”) Privacy Policy. Our services are designed to offer users (collectively, "User", “Users,” “you,” or “your”) the opportunity to easily track, follow and share publicly available flight data with other Users (“Services”). The Services are provided to you through our website (“Site”), mobile applications (“App”,"Apps") and other digital platforms ("Other") owned and/or controlled by AirNav. 

This Privacy Policy explains what personal data we collect through the Services, how we use and share that data, and your choices concerning our data practices. 

By providing us with your personal data when using the Services, including through the use of cookies, you agree to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use the Services. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form in our Site, Apps or Other. 

When ordering or registering on our Services, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, use our Services anonymously in some cases. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs 

\- To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

\- For direct marketing purposes   
The email address you provide may be used to send you information, offers and promotions, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) regarding that transaction will not be kept on file for more than 60 days. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and for other uses in order to provide you the best possible experience of our Services. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**EUROPEAN UNION (EU) USERS - General Data Protection Regulation Compliance**

Scope. This section applies if you are a User in the EU (for these purposes, reference to the EU also includes the European Economic Area countries of Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway). 

Data Controller. AirNav Systems LLC is the data controller for processing Personal Data provided to us through our Services. To find out our contact details, please see the “Contact Us” section below. 

Your Rights. Subject to applicable EU law, you have the following rights in relation to your Personal Data: 

\- Right of access: If you ask us, we will confirm whether we are processing your Personal Data and, if so, provide you with a copy of that Personal Data along with certain other details. If you require additional copies, we may need to charge a reasonable fee. 

\- Right to rectification: If your Personal Data is inaccurate or incomplete, you are entitled to ask that we correct or complete it. If we shared your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the correction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly. 

\- Right to erasure: You may ask us to delete or remove your Personal Data, such as where you withdraw your consent. If we shared your data with others, we will tell them about the erasure where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data with so you can contact them directly. 

\- Right to restrict processing: You may ask us to restrict or ‘block’ the processing of your Personal Data in certain circumstances, such as where you contest the accuracy of the data or object to us processing it (please read below for information on your right to object). We will tell you before we lift any restriction on processing. If we shared your Personal Data with others, we will tell them about the restriction where possible. If you ask us, and where possible and lawful to do so, we will also tell you with whom we shared your Personal Data so you can contact them directly. 

\- Right to data portability: You have the right to obtain your Personal Data from us that you consented to give us or that was provided to us as necessary in connection with our contract with you. We will give you your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. You may reuse it elsewhere. 

\- Right to object: You may ask us at any time to stop processing your Personal Data, and we will do so: 

If we are relying on a legitimate interest to process your Personal Data -- unless we demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing or If we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing. \- Right to withdraw consent:If we rely on your consent to process your Personal Data, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. Withdrawal of consent will not affect any processing of your data before we received notice that you wished to withdraw consent. 

\- Right to lodge a complaint with the data protection authority: If you have a concern about our privacy practices, including the way we handled your Personal Data, you can report it to the data protection authority that is authorized to hear those concerns. 

Please see the “Contact Us” section below for information on how to contact us to exercise your rights. 

Legitimate Interest. “Legitimate interests” means our interests in conducting our business, managing and delivering the best Services to you. This Privacy Policy describes when we process your Personal Data for our legitimate interests, what these interests are and your rights. We will not use your Personal Data for activities where the impact on you overrides our interests, unless we have your consent or those activities are otherwise required or permitted to by law. 

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.radarbox24.com/terms-of-use 

**Your Consent**

By using our Site, Apps or Other, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**CONTACT US**

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about AirNav’s Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Services. 

You may contact us as follows: You may send an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), or send mail to: 

AirNav Systems LLC  
1228 East 7th Avenue  
Tampa, FL 33605, USA
